RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
- II. Press Relations/Media Activities, 1983-2005; 3.0 boxes; (3 linear feet)
  - B. Press Releases, 1983-2003; 531 folders and 6 electronic files
    - Speaker Murphy, C. Watts, February 22, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 247)
    - Eugene Tillman, W. Smith, B. DeLoach, March 2, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 248)
    - N.R.A., Grace Davis, March 2, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 249)
    - Tommy Smith, March 7, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 250)
    - Hinson Mosley, March 8, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 251)
    - Larry Walker, March 9, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 252)
    - Carl Rogers, March 9, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 253)
    - Jeanette Jamieson, March 9, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 254)
    - Kem Shipp, March 16, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 255)
    - Ann Purcell, March 20, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 256)
    - Jay Shaw, March 20, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 257)
    - Dorothy Pelote, March 20, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 258)
    - Roger Byrd, March 20, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 259)
    - Bob Holmes, April 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 260)
    - Henry Reaves, April 6, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 261)
    - Newt Hudson, April 6, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 262)
    - Richard Royal, April 6, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 263)
    - Roger Byrd, May 15, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 264)
    - Butch Parrish, May 15, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 265)
    - Terry Coleman, May 25, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 266)
    - [Mike Snow, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 267)
    - [Van Streat, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 268)
    - [Paul Smith, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 269)
    - Jerry Lifsey, May 29, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 270)
    - Jere Johnson, May 29, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 271)
    - John Godbee, May 29, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 272)
    - Carl Von Epps, May 29, 1995 (Box II.2, Folder 273)
    - [Mikey Channell, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 274)
    - [Sonny Dixon, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 275)
    - [Jeff Williams, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 276)
    - [Ben Whitaker, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 277)
    - [Gene Tillman, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 278)
    - [Henson Mosley, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 279)
    - [Denny Dobbs, May 29, 1995] (Box II.2, Folder 280)
    - Billy Randall, January 23, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 281)
    - Sharon Falls, January 25, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 282)
    - Grace Davis, March 5, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 283)
    - Henry Reaves, April 11, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 284)
    - Newt Hudson, April 11, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 285)
    - Richard Royal, April 11, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 286)
    - Gail Buckner, May 8, 1996 (Box II.2, Folder 287)
    - [Jeanette Jamieson, May 24, 2000] (Box II.2, Folder 288)
    - [Able Mable Thomas, September 29, 2003] (Box II.2, Folder 289)
    - Funding for Firefighting Training Tower [User copy available, JamiesonBFDtower.pdf], May 24, 2000 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Funding for Franklin Foresters Society [User copy available, Jamiesonforestmoney.pdf], May 24, 2000 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Funding for Lavonia Police Department [User copy available, JamiesonLPDweapons.pdf], May 24, 2000 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Funding for Toccoa Fire Department [User copy available, JamiesonTFDlaptop.pdf], May 24, 2000 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Hearings on improving child protection laws [User copy available, Squires,juvenile.pdf], May 24, 2000 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Rep. Able Mable Thomas convenes public hearing, [User copy available, Thomas.pdf], September 29, 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
  - C. Radio Scripts, 1990-2005; 14 folders and 7 electronic files
    This sub-series consists of daily radio scripts, 1990-2005, that provide summaries of important House votes and legislation. This sub-series lacks scripts for 1992, 2001, and 2004.
    - Radio Scripts, [January 12, 1990 – March 8, 1990] (Box II.3, Folder 1)
    - Representative Scripts, 1991 (Box II.3, Folder 2)
    - Daily Feeds, [January 11, 1993 – March 23, 1993] (Box II.3, Folder 3)
    - 1994 Legislative Feeds, [January 11, 1994 – March 14, 1994] (Box II.3, Folder 4)
    - News Feeds, [January 23, 1995 – September 9, 1995] (Box II.3, Folder 5)
    - News Feeds, [January 26, 1996 – February 28, 1996] (Box II.3, Folder 6)
    - 1997 News Feeds, [January 9, 1997 – March 28, 1997] (Box II.3, Folder 7)
    - 1998 News Feeds, [January 9 – March 19] (Box II.3, Folder 8)
    - 1999 News Feeds, [January 8, 1999 – March 24, 1999] (Box II.3, Folder 9)
    - 2000 News Feeds, [January 24, 2000 – March 21, 2000] (Box II.3, Folder 10)
    - 2002 Daily Feeds, [January 14, 2002 – January 30, 2002] (Box II.3, Folder 11)
    - 2002 Daily Feeds February thru End of Session, [February 1, 2002 – April 9, 2002] (Box II.3, Folder 12)
    - [News Feeds], February 2003 (Box II.3, Folder 13)
    - Special Session Scripts, undated (Box II.3, Folder 14)
    - News feed reporting measures addressed at Georgia House of Representatives meeting [User Copy, news_feed_2003Feb2.pdf ], February 2, 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
    - News feed by Rep. Ellis Black reporting measures addressed at Georgia House of Representatives meeting [User Copy, news_feed_2003Feb28.pdf ], February 28, 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Report on Fiscal Year 2004 budget for Georgia [User Copy, budget_2003April7.pdf ], circa 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Report on state budget for Georgia [User Copy, budget_FY2004.pdf], April 7, 2003 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Report on Fiscal Year 2005 budget for Georgia [User Copy, budget_FY2005.pdf ], circa 2004 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Report on Fiscal Year 2005 budget for Georgia [User Copy, budget_FY2005.pdf ], circa 2004 (Item EM-362-367)
    - Georgia educational system reform, [User Copy, education.pdf], undated (Item EM-362-367)
- III. Member Files, 1971-2006; 8.0 boxes; (8 linear feet)
  Member Files are organized into three sub-series based on item type: A. Biographical Files, B. Photographs, and C. Directories. The photographic materials have been separated from the biographical files for the purpose of preservation; however, both biographical files and the corresponding photographs are arranged alphabetically by the member’s last name and are cross referenced. Additional photographs of Georgia House of Representative members and events are located in Series VII: Photographs.
  - A. Biographical Files, 1975-2004; 295.0 folders
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically and includes House members’ biographical sketches, press releases, and speeches. Corresponding photographs have been separated for preservation purposes and may be found in sub-series B. Photographs.
    - Members List, 1975-1976 (Box III.1, Folder 1)
    - [Members/Committees – House of Representatives, 1987-1988] (Box III.1, Folder 2)
    - Ex-Representatives Biographical Sketches, 1987 (Box III.1, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Sketches, 1988 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box III.1, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Sketches, 1988 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box III.1, Folder 5)
    - [Biographies – No Longer Serving], [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 6)
    - Betty Aaron, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 7)
    - Ralph David Abernathy, [September 5, 1989-April 10, 1991] (Box III.1, Folder 8)
    - G. D. Adams, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 9)
    - Marvin Adams, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 10)
    - Fred Aiken, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 11)
    - Dean Alford, [January 21, 1985 – December 21, 1989] (Box III.1, Folder 12)
    - Benjamin Allen, [January 12, 1996 – June 3, 1999] (Box III.1, Folder 13)
    - Ray Allen, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 14)
    - Wendell T. Anderson, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 15)
    - Bob Argo, [September 12, 1983 – April 14, 1984 (Box III.1, Folder 16)
    - Troy Athon, [January 21, 1985 – June 23, 1986] (Box III.1, Folder 17)
    - Bill Atkins, [August 24, 1993] (Box III.1, Folder 18)
    - Deal Auten, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 19)
    - Frank Bailey, [September 8, 1994 – February 23, 1999] (Box III.1, Folder 20)
    - Thurbert Baker, [July 18, 1991] (Box III.1, Folder 21)
    - Ralph James Balkom, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 22)
    - Charles Banister, [October 8, 2002] (Box III.1, Folder 23)
    - Fisher Barfoot, [July 17, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 24)
    - Emory E. Bargerson, [December 29, 1995 – January 2, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 25)
    - Ray Barnes, [September 8, 1994 – January 17, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 26)
    - Bill Barnett, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 27)
    - Michael Barnett, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 28)
    - Kermit Bates, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 29)
    - James Beck, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 30)
    - Pat Bell, [January 9, 2001 – July 25, 2001] (Box III.1, Folder 31)
    - Jimmy Benefield, [July 30, 1989 – November 19, 1999] (Box III.1, Folder 32)
    - Lorenzo Benn, [November 27, 1989 – June 4, 1990] (Box III.1, Folder 33)
    - Ken Birdsong, [January 20, 1995 – May 4, 2004] (Box III.1, Folder 34)
    - Sanford Bishop, [November 19, 1983] (Box III.1, Folder 35)
    - Mike Boggs, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 36)
    - Paul Bolster, [January 6, 1982 – March 7, 1986] (Box III.1, Folder 37)
    - Henry Bostick, [December 21, 1993 – April 8, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 38)
    - Paul Branch, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 39)
    - Claude Bray, [March 6, 1984] (Box III.1, Folder 40)
    - Keith Breedlove, [January 23, 1997 - June 10, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 41)
    - Craig Brock, [November 14, 2003] (Box III.1, Folder 42)
    - Donna Brooks, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 43)
    - Hugh D. Broome, [January 9, 2001 – March 26, 2004] (Box III.1, Folder 44)
    - George Brown, [February 2, 1994 – October 17, 1995] (Box III.1, Folder 45)
    - Joey Brush, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 46)
    - Thomas Buck, [June 15, 1995 – March 20, 2003] (Box III.1, Folder 47)
    - Barbara Bunn, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 48)
    - Roger Byrd, [July 18, 1991 – May 2, 2001] (Box III.1, Folder 49)
    - Tom Campbell, [April 24, 1993 - March 24, 2003] (Box III.1, Folder 50)
    - Henrietta Canty, [September 3, 1993 – September 8, 1993] (Box III.1, Folder 51)
    - John Carlisle, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 52)
    - Tyrone Carrell, [October 26, 1993] (Box III.1, Folder 53)
    - Hanson Carter, [March 3, 1985 – February 8, 1995] (Box III.1, Folder 54)
    - Tom Cauthorn, [September 7, 1993 – June 23, 1994] (Box III.1, Folder 55)
    - John M. Chafin, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 56)
    - Tommy Chambless, [January 1, 1989 – July 1, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 57)
    - George Chance, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 58)
    - Donald E. Cheeks, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 59)
    - Buddy Childers, [July 13, 1985 – May 21, 2004] (Box III.1, Folder 60)
    - Peggy Childs, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 61)
    - Louis Clark, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 62)
    - Steven Clark, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 63)
    - William Clark, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 64)
    - Lynda Coker, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 65)
    - Luther Colbert, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 66)
    - Ginger Collins, [January 9, 2001] (Box III.1, Folder 67)
    - Carlton Colwell, [September 24, 1993] (Box III.1, Folder 68)
    - Jack Connell, [April 12, 2004 - January 10, 2002] (Box III.1, Folder 69)
    - Barbara Couch, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 70)
    - Cathy Cox, [June 13, 1994 – February 12, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 71)
    - Kathy Cox, [February 21, 2000 – September 21, 2000] (Box III.1, Folder 72)
    - Walter Cox, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 73)
    - John G. Crawford, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 74)
    - Ronald Allen Crews, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 75)
    - Tom Crosby, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 76)
    - Ronnie Culbreth, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 77)
    - Mary Young Cummings, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 78)
    - Grace Davis, [January 20, 1993 – March 15, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 79)
    - Max Davis, [July 23, 2002] (Box III.1, Folder 80)
    - Douglas Dean, [April 30, 1985] (Box III.1, Folder 81)
    - Buddy DeLoach, [March 2, 1995 – March 21, 2001] (Box III.1, Folder 82)
    - George DeLoach, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 83)
    - Scott Dix, [July 17, 1997 – May 19, 1998] (Box III.1, Folder 84)
    - Harry Dixon, [September 24, 1993 – January 23, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 85)
    - Sonny Dixon, [September 24, 1993 – January 23, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 86)
    - Denny Dobbs, [January 21, 1995 – March 7, 1997] (Box III.1, Folder 87)
    - Bill Dover, [May 23, 198 – April 13, 1993] (Box III.1, Folder 88)
    - Wesley Dunn, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 89)
    - Ward Edward, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 90)
    - Wayne Elliot, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 91)
    - Lawton Evans, [undated (Box III.1, Folder 92)
    - Mike Evans, [November 18, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 93)
    - Doug Everett, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 94)
    - Dorothy Felton, [August 8, 1981 – June 12, 1995] (Box III.1, Folder 95)
    - Jimmy Floyd, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 96)
    - Paul Foster, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 97)
    - Mary Jane Galer, [May 18, 1984] (Box III.1, Folder 98)
    - John Godbee, [March 19, 1993 - May 20, 1996] (Box III.1, Folder 99)
    - Tim Golden, [November 27, 1995] (Box III.1, Folder 100)
    - Willard Goodwin, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 101)
    - George Green, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 102)
    - John W. Greer, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 103)
    - Jim Griffin, [undated] (Box III.1, Folder 104)
    - George Grindley, [February 25, 1995] (Box III.1, Folder 105)
    - Denmark Grover, [1994 June 10] (Box III.1, Folder 106)
    - DeWayne Hamilton, [June 30, 1983 – February 5, 1991] (Box III.2, Folder 1)
    - John Hammond, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 2)
    - Sally Harrell, [March 23, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 3)
    - Bobby Harris, [September 24, 1993] (Box III.2, Folder 4)
    - Jed Harris, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 5)
    - Melanie Harris, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 6)
    - Bettieanne Hart, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 7)
    - Paul Heard, [July 18, 1991] (Box III.2, Folder 8)
    - Greg Hecht, [June 19, 1997 – July 14, 1997] (Box III.2, Folder 9)
    - June Hegstrom, [January 28, 1993 – July 7, 2000] (Box III.2, Folder 10)
    - Bill Hembree, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 11)
    - Charles E. Holcomb, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 12)
    - Ray Holland, [September 16, 1997] (Box III.2, Folder 13)
    - George Hooks, [February 28, 1986 – March 30, 1990] (Box III.2, Folder 14)
    - Frank Horne, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 15)
    - Charles Gresham Howren, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 16)
    - Ralph Hudgens, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 17)
    - Newt Hudson, [June 10, 1994 – September 20, 2002] (Box III.2, Folder 18)
    - Robert Irvin, [October 18, 1995 – August 28, 1998] (Box III.2, Folder 19)
    - Johnny Isakson, [February 6, 1984 – January 16, 1986] (Box III.2, Folder 20)
    - Bill Jackson, [June 15, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 21)
    - Jerry Jackson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 22)
    - Neal Jackson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 23)
    - Curtis Jenkins, [April 17, 1989 – September 10, 2002] (Box III.2, Folder 24)
    - Diane Johnson, [September 8, 1993] (Box III.2, Folder 25)
    - Dorothy Johnson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 26)
    - Eric Johnson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 27)
    - Jere Johnson, [May 29, 1995] (Box III.2, Folder 28)
    - Rudolph Johnson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 29)
    - Suzi Johnson, [July 18, 1991] (Box III.2, Folder 30)
    - Teresa Green – Johnson, [February 25, 2003 – April 28, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 31)
    - Tony Johnson, [January 9, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 32)
    - Ralph Johnston, [February 2, 1993 – February 20, 1995] (Box III.2, Folder 33)
    - Sydney Jones, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 34)
    - Vernon Jones, [January 14, 1994 – December 12, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 35)
    - Brian Joyce, [February 17, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 36)
    - Mitchell Kaye, [October 18, 1995 – June 3, 1998] (Box III.2, Folder 37)
    - Tom Kilgore, [May 23, 1984 – June 23, 1989] (Box III.2, Folder 38)
    - Glynda King, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 39)
    - Jack Kingston, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 40)
    - Gregory Kinnamon, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 41)
    - Edward Klein, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 42)
    - Tom Knox, [January 9, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 43)
    - Daniel Lackly, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 44)
    - Dick Lane, [June 1, 1991] (Box III.2, Folder 45)
    - Craig Lanier, [January 9, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 46)
    - Beverly Langford, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 47)
    - Jerry Lawler, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 48)
    - Tom Lawrence, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 49)
    - Robert Lawson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 50)
    - Bill Lee, [January 16, 1995 – May 19, 1998] (Box III.2, Folder 51)
    - Carolyn Lee, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 52)
    - Jerry Lifsey, [May 29, 1995] (Box III.2, Folder 53)
    - John Linder, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 54)
    - Bobby Long, [November 26, 1987] (Box III.2, Folder 55)
    - John Lupton, [January 31, 1989] (Box III.2, Folder 56)
    - George Maddox, [February 28, 2001 – June 9, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 57)
    - J. C. Maddox, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 58)
    - Leland Maddox, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 59)
    - Bill Mangum, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 60)
    - Harold Mann, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 61)
    - Chris Martin, [June 1, 1984] (Box III.2, Folder 62)
    - Jim Martin, [August 1989 – March 13, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 63)
    - Warren Massey, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 64)
    - Hugh Matthews, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 65)
    - Louis McBee, [June 6, 1994 – March 22, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 66)
    - Bubba McDonald, [March 28, 1978 – February 19, 1990] (Box III.2, Folder 67)
    - Forrest McKelvey, [May 9, 1984] (Box III.2, Folder 68)
    - Billy McKinney, [April 30, 1985 – April 23, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 69)
    - Cynthia McKinney, [February 11, 1992] (Box III.2, Folder 70)
    - Leonard “Nookie” Meadows, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 71)
    - John Merritt, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 72)
    - Anne Meuller, [February 4, 1993 – March 22, 2002] (Box III.2, Folder 73)
    - Wade Milam, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 74)
    - Billy Milford, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 75)
    - Barbara Mobley, [September 17, 1993 – April 18, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 76)
    - John Mobley, [June 10, 1994] (Box III.2, Folder 77)
    - Lunsford Moody, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 78)
    - James Moore, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 79)
    - Emily Morsberger, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 80)
    - Chesley Morton, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 81)
    - Roy Moultrie, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 82)
    - Clinton Oliver, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 83)
    - Donald Oliver, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 84)
    - Margaret Oliver, [August 16, 1989] (Box III.2, Folder 85)
    - Earl O’Neal, [September 10, 1998 – August 5, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 86)
    - Easton Orr, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 87)
    - Mike Padgett, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 88)
    - James Pannell, [October 1986 – February 16, 1989] (Box III.2, Folder 89)
    - Larry Parrish, [July 18, 1991] (Box III.2, Folder 90)
    - Bob Patten, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 91)
    - Dorothy Pelote, [May 14, 1993 – March 1, 2002] (Box III.2, Folder 92)
    - Tim Perry, [September 8, 1994 – January 23, 1997] (Box III.2, Folder 93)
    - Robert Peters, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 94)
    - Boyd Pettit, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 95)
    - Pete Phillips, [June 1, 1982] (Box III.2, Folder 96)
    - Garland Pinholster, [November 18, 1996] (Box III.2, Folder 97)
    - Frank Pinkston, [June 5, 1978 – June 9, 1986] (Box III.2, Folder 98)
    - Judy Poag, [April 14, 2000] (Box III.2, Folder 99)
    - Don Ponder, [August 19, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 100)
    - Ken Poston, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 101)
    - C. J. Powell, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 102)
    - Ann Purcell, [February 1, 1995 – March 8, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 103)
    - Benjamin Purcell, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 104)
    - Arnold Ragas, [March 28, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 105)
    - Howard Rainey, [January 21, 1981] (Box III.2, Folder 106)
    - Tom Ramsey, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 107)
    - Virginia Ramsey, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 108)
    - Billy Randall, [March 25, 1993 – February 9, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 109)
    - Mamie Randolph, [July 7, 1988] (Box III.2, Folder 110)
    - Harry Reaves, [October 15, 1993 – May 29, 2000] (Box III.2, Folder 111)
    - Frank Redding, [December 29, 1989] (Box III.2, Folder 112)
    - Robert Reichert, [June 7, 1995 – November 17, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 113)
    - Kasim Reid, [December 7, 2000] (Box III.2, Folder 114)
    - Eleanor Richardson, [August 10, 1988] (Box III.2, Folder 115)
    - Danae Roberts, [January 9, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 116)
    - Lawrence Roberts, [January 23, 1997 – July 7, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 117)
    - Cas Robinson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 118)
    - Pete Robinson, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 119)
    - Chip Rogers, [January 22, 2003] (Box III.2, Folder 120)
    - Barron Ross, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 121)
    - Randy Sauder, [January 23, 1997 – July 2, 1997] (Box III.2, Folder 122)
    - Stephen Scarlett, [June 3, 1999] (Box III.2, Folder 123)
    - Chuck Scheid, [June 5, 1998] (Box III.2, Folder 124)
    - Wallace Scholar, [January 13, 2001 – June 1, 2004] (Box III.2, Folder 125)
    - John Scoggins, [June 7, 1995 – November 27, 1995] (Box III.2, Folder 126)
    - Valencia Seay, [January 9, 2001 – December 4, 2001] (Box III.2, Folder 127)
    - Helen Selman, [undated] (Box III.2, Folder 128)
    - Tom Shanahan, [June 5, 1997 – October 18, 2002] (Box III.2, Folder 129)
    - J. Neal Shepard, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 1)
    - Thomas Sherrill, [June 13, 1995 – October 18, 1996] (Box III.3, Folder 2)
    - Allen Sherrod, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 3)
    - Kem Shipp, [February 13, 1995 – February 10, 1998] (Box III.3, Folder 4)
    - John Simpson, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 5)
    - Earleen Sizemore, [March 31, 1986] (Box III.3, Folder 6)
    - Jimmy Skipper, [June 7, 1994 – May 7, 2004] (Box III.3, Folder 7)
    - Charlie Smith, [August 30, 1993 – April 22, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 8)
    - Clint Smith, [June 3, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 9)
    - Larry Smith, [August 18, 1993 – August 31, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 10)
    - Willow Smith, [August 1988 – August 9, 1995] (Box III.3, Folder 11)
    - Bob Snelling, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 12)
    - Mike Snow, [February 20, 1986 – October 6, 2004] (Box III.3, Folder 13)
    - Mary Squires, [May 24, 2000 – September 20, 2002] (Box III.3, Folder 14)
    - Tracy Stallings, [January 17, 1997 – October 30, 2000] (Box III.3, Folder 15)
    - Frank Stancil, [July 2, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 16)
    - Steve Stancil, [January 22, 1997 – May 30, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 17)
    - Pamela Stanley, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 18)
    - Cathey W. Steinberg, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 19)
    - Tommy Stephenson, [October 26, 1993] (Box III.3, Folder 20)
    - Jim Stokes, [June 15, 2001 – November 19, 2003] (Box III.3, Folder 21)
    - Van Streat, [January 7, 1993 – February 19, 1996] (Box III.3, Folder 22)
    - Maretta Taylor, [August 9, 1995] (Box III.3, Folder 23)
    - Doug Taper, [December 22, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 24)
    - Charles Thomas, [May 1989 – April 14, 1994] (Box III.3, Folder 25)
    - Maple Thomas, [January 21, 1985] (Box III.3, Folder 26)
    - Regina Thomas, [February 16, 1995 – December 15, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 27)
    - Curt Thompson, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 28)
    - Eugene Tillman, [February 13, 1995 – September 6, 2002] (Box III.3, Folder 29)
    - Theo Titus, [December 21, 1993 – January 23, 1997] (Box III.3, Folder 30)
    - Claude T. “Tommy” Tolbert, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 31)
    - Scott Tolbert, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 32)
    - Matthew Taylor, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 33)
    - Kil Townsend, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 34)
    - Sharon Trense, [August 30, 1993 – November 16, 1999] (Box III.3, Folder 35)
    - Tom Triplett, [undated] (Box III.3, Folder 36)